SHREYASH MUSALE

3 Chatterley Court, Wragby Road, Nottingham, NG7 2AY ● 07833863151 ● musaleshreyash@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shreyash-musale-398600178/

Professional Summary

As a software developer with 4 years of experience and a diverse skill set, I'm well-versed in various technologies and programming languages such as Python, Java, JavaScript, and SQL. My analytical skills and logical thinking ability have enabled me to work effectively with reputed organizations such as Wipro, E&Y, and BlackRock. I am currently pursuing a Master's degree in Computer Science from Nottingham Trent University, further enhancing my technical expertise. Additionally, my excellent communication skills make me an asset to any team. I am actively seeking an opportunity to leverage my skills and experience to make a positive impact in the software industry. With my passion for technology and desire to innovate, I would be an excellent addition to any company looking for a motivated software developer.

Skills

- Python
- Java, JavaFX
- HTML
- JavaScript
- SQL
- Oracle Server

- Django
- PandasNumPy
- Sklearn
- Machine Learning
- Redis
- Microsoft Azure
- Apache Tomcat
- Docker
- RESTful Services
- API Development

Work History

Senior Software Developer Mphasis/BlackRock - Pune, India

02/2022 - 08/2022

Worked on large datasets (of financial domain) to create Blueprints of portfolios in an in-house tool called GP Report Seeder.

- Collaborated with the team members based in different part of world to deliver features and backend logic of an in-house product of BlackRock.
- Worked extensively on large datasets using python, pandas and Sybase to operate on data which could be used as input as per requirements.
- Developed and timely delivered tool features through a sprint-based development approach.

Senior Software Engineer Msys Technologies/ Ernst & Youngs - Pune, India

02/2021 - 02/2022

I worked as a part of a team named Asterisk with different co-workers for the supply chain domain project.

- Took technical ownership of tools named SCP and SDP and developed backend logic and REST API endpoints of the tools.
- Handled maintenance and deployment of tools on Prod server.

• My role also included work like writing data pipelines and creating and maintaining databases according to client feature requirement.

Project Engineer 08/2018 - 12/2020

Wipro Technologies - Pune, India

I joined Wipro as a fresh graduate and worked in roles ranging from assisting a senior developer to working as an individual on a task. Most of the tasks included here were automating tedious manual tasks to save time

- Developed automated application which can segregate several URLs to check if they are already present on URL Blocking device.
- Developed a python-based tools to test bunch of URLs to see if they are active or not and writing its status on excel.

Education

Master of Science: Computer Science
NOTTINGHAM TRENT UNIVERSITY — Nottingham
Relevant modules Included:

- Advanced Software Engineering
- System Analysis and Design
- Service Oriented Cloud Architecture

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Science **SAVITRIBAI PHULE PUNE UNIVERSITY** — Pune, India Relevant modules Included:

- Data Structure
- Theory of Computation

- Mobile Interactive Systems
- Applied AI and Data mining

08/2014 - 07/2018

09/2022 - 09/2023

- Software Design Methodologies
- Operating system design

Projects

Cloud Based file management system

Module Project

Developed a file management desktop application using java and docker where user can store his files on cloud and can easily retrieve them whenever he wants. User can also create new file or open existing file and edit. **Technology Stack** – Java, JavaFX, MySql, Docker, Jsch

GitHub Link - https://olympuss.ntu.ac.uk/N1113049/JavaFXApp

Stock Market Website Module Project

Developed a stock market website using Python and REST APIs where user can analyse and buy stocks. **Technology Stack** – Python, Django, REST API, docker, Tomcat server, MySql

GitHub Link - https://github.com/shreyashm18/stockRestApiCoursework

Student Traveller Photo Blogging Android App

Module Project

Developed an android app for students and travellers where they can upload a photo and write a blog about it. **Technology Stack** – Android Studio, Java, Firebase

GitHub Link - https://github.com/shreyashm18/AndroidStudentTraveller

Extra Curricular

- Created a python bot to fetch available vaccine slots in Pune, India and to send them to a channel n telegram.
- Created a web project where I can see COVID report (Used free API service) according to country, date range and also statistic of COVID patients.
- Created a chat application using Django where I used Redis channel layer.

Part-Time Activities:

Worked as cook staff at KFC.

• Worked as warehouse operative at Riverside bakery